MINJUNG KIM

■ minjung.kim@vision.snu.ac.kr | Google scholar | LinkedIn | GitHub | minnjung.github.io

♀ 317, Bldg 138, 1 Gwanak-ro, Gwanak-gu, Seoul, Korea

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in the field of **Visual Localization** and **3D Dense Captioning**, especially about (i) understanding the scene from images and point clouds, (ii) dealing with multi-modalities, and (iii) utilizing high-level semantic information for place recognition and 3D dense captioning.

EDUCATION

Seoul National University	Seoul, Korea
Integrated M.S./Ph.D. Student in Computer Science and Engineering; (GPA: 4.03/4.3)	Mar. 2018 – Current
Vision and Learning lab, advised by Prof. Gunhee Kim.	
Sogang University	Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering; **(GPA: 3.58/4.3), Magna Cum Laude**Mar. 2014 – Feb. 2018

Advised by Prof. Hyukjun Lee.

PUBLICATIONS

Bi-directional Contextual Attention for 3D Dense Captioning Minjung Kim, Hyung Suk Lim, Soonyoung Lee, Bumsoo Kim*, Gunhee Kim*	ECCV 2024 Oral presentation
Rethinking the Role of Queries in 3D Dense Captioning Minjung Kim, Gunhee Kim	KCC 2024
See It All: Contextualized Late Aggregation for 3D Dense Captioning Minjung Kim, Hyung Suk Lim, Seung Hwan Kim, Soonyoung Lee, Bumsoo Kim*, Gunhee Kim*	ACL 2024 Findings
EP2P-Loc: End-to-End 3D Point to 2D Pixel Localization for Large-Scale Visual Localization Minjung Kim, Junseo Koo, Gunhee Kim	ICCV 2023
Indoor/Outdoor Transition Recognition Based on Door Detection Seohyun Jeon, Minjung Kim, Seunghwan Park, Jaeyoung Lee	UR 2022
Drop-Bottleneck: Learning Discrete Compressed Representation for Noise-Robust Exploration Jaekyeom Kim, Minjung Kim, Dongyeon Woo, Gunhee Kim	ICLR 2021
Logo Detection and Recognition Algorithm using YOLO-v3 Model Minjung Kim, Sungen Kim, Gunhee Kim	CICS 2020
Memorization Precedes Generation: Learning Unsupervised GANs with Memory Networks Youngjin Kim, Minjung Kim, Gunhee Kim	ICLR 2018
Machine Learning for Determining Duplicate Question Minjung Kim, Yeongjoon Park, Hyungsuk Lim, Jihoon Yang	KSC 2017
Sketch based Face Image Generation with Text Mapping Minjung Kim, Hyungsuk Lim, Yeongjoon Park, Yeseul Joo, MyoungWan Koo	KSC 2017

• The DeepGuider Project is a national government-funded research project focused on developing a navigation guidance system for robots to navigate urban environments without pre-mapping.

• I contribute to finding clues to locate autonomous robots by detecting and recognizing points of interests (POIs) in images of a scene, including text, landmarks, and doors for indoor-outdoor transition, while also developing robust training methods for environmental changes.

PRIDE: 3D Place Recognition In Dynamic Environment | GitHub

Mar. 2022 - Current

- This work proposes a new dataset called PRIDE, which includes dynamic objects such as cars and pedestrians, for 3D place recognition in dynamic environments that are more realistic and challenging than current benchmark datasets.
- The proposed PRIDE-Net architecture with a new loss function focuses on extracting discriminative global descriptors and capturing global context using spatial information, while being robust to dynamic environments.
- Experiments on the PRIDE dataset and existing benchmarks show that our proposed method outperforms previous methods and that each proposed module effectively improves performance.
- The code will be released after acceptance.

FCAT: Fully Convolutional Network with Self-Attention for Point Cloud based Place Recognition

Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2022

- We construct a novel network named FCAT (Fully Convolutional network with a self-ATtention unit) that can generate a discriminative and context-aware global descriptor for place recognition from the 3D point cloud.
- It features with a novel sparse fully convolutional network architecture with sparse tensors for extracting informative local geometric features computed in a single pass. It also involves a self-attention module for 3D point cloud to encode local context information between local descriptors.

Bayesian Deep Learning course | Lecture

Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2018

- To understand deep learning papers, we explain the basic concepts of probability and Bayesian, and introduce papers related to Bayesian neural networks.
- This lecture can be taken through *edwith* of Naver Connect.

Sketch based Face Image Generation with Text Mapping | GitHub

Sep. 2017 - Feb. 2018

- A typical sketch might have been uncomfortable when a person or program was used to map a person's features in detail. This process is limited not only because it is very complex and requires technicians, but also because it creates a feeling of incompatibility with real people.
- This program, named Metamon, makes a picture of a person's face by entering the image of the border sketch of the person's face and the text information that shows the characteristics of the face.

Arduino & Raspberry Pi & Internet of Things (IoT) Tutorial | Project page

Dec. 2016 - Mar. 2017

- I create tutorial pages with Youtube videos and code for beginners in Arduino kit and Raspberry Pi development.
- I also introduce the concept of the Internet of Things (IoT) and work on a mini-project using *ThingSpeak*™.

Sogang Navigation and Introduction (SNI) | Github

Mar. 2015 - Jul. 2015

- We develop a navigation system that introduces the internal facilities of each building and displays the shortest route and time from building to building using the Floyd-Washall algorithm.
- To build data for the development, we measured the time taken by walking directly on each path.

EXPERIENCES

Vision and Multimodal Lab

LG AI Research

Research Intern

Jun. 2023 – May. 2024

KDB-SNU AI course Seoul National University

Teaching Assistant Apr. 2023

2022-3 SK hynix ML Engineer courseSeoul National University

Teaching Assistant

Nov. 2022 – Dec. 2022

KDB-SNU AI courseSeoul National UniversityTeaching AssistantApr. 2022 – May. 2022

LG AI core human resource training course

Seoul National University

Teaching Assistant

Feb. 2022

loT · Artificial Intelligence · Big Data (IAB) course

Seoul National University

Teaching Assistant Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2019

Bayesian Deep Learning courseNaver ConnectPublisherFeb. 2018 – Jul. 2018

Vision and Learning LaboratorySeoul National UniversityResearch InternJul. 2017 – Feb. 2018

Biointelligence LaboratorySeoul National UniversityResearch InternSep. 2016 – Feb. 2017

Arduino & Raspberry Pi Kit DeveloperMakeWith (Startup)Development InternDec. 2016 – Jan. 2017

AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS

Animal Datathon Korea Animal Tech Korea

Predicting joint coordinates of a cow for pose estimation; **2nd place**Jul. 2021

Samsung Humantech Paper AwardSamsung ElectronicsSignal Processing section; Silver prizeFeb. 2021

KSC 2017 Paper AwardKorean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers
The undergraduate/junior thesis contest award

Feb. 2018

Magna Cum Laude HonorSogang UniversityAcademic HonorsFeb. 2018

Academic Excellence Scholarship

Academic Honors

Sogang University

Jul. 2017 – Feb. 2018

Windows 10 IoT Core & Microsoft Azure for Microsoft IoT Solution Competition

Microsoft

Implementing Internet of Things (IoT) projects with Windows 10 IoT Core and Microsoft Azure; 10th place Apr. 2017

SKILLS

Programming: Python, C, C++

Frameworks: Pytorch, TensorFlow/Keras **Tools:** Git, VSCode, Vim, Docker, Slurm

Others: Arduino, Rapsberry Pi

Reviewer of international conferences

- European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV) 2024
- IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) 2023
- IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023
- Asian Conference on Computer Vision (ACCV) 2022
- International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2022, 2023
- Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) 2021, 2022, 2023, 2024

Technical Coaching

• 2022-3 SK hynix ML Engineer Technical Coaching